Hey!
喂!
Come on!
來啊!
Stop!
停下來!
That's my camera! That's my camera!
那是我的相機! 那是我的相機!
Stop them!
停下來!
You bastards!
你這個混蛋!
Sorry.
不好意思
Thank you.
謝謝
You, are the worst beach boy I know.
你, 是我認識最差勁的海灘男孩
I am simply the best at being the worst.
我是把差勁表現得最淋漓盡致的那個
I am bored.
我好無聊
You are often bored, Mbwana.
你常常覺得很無聊, 波瓦那
The same beachy, the same sun, the same life.
一樣的海灘, 一樣的陽光, 一樣的人生
We need to build something in this town, no?
我們應該這個鎮上蓋點什麼, 不是嗎?
What we need is tourist dollars,
我們需要的是觀光財,
and we won't get tourist dollars
但我們沒辦法從現在的白人
thieving from the few Muzungu we have, eh?
身上賺到觀光財, 對吧?
The tourists we have are not good enough.
我們現在的觀光根本不夠
We need to change things, eh?
我們需要改變, 對吧?
We need to build something wild here.
我們要在這裡蓋一些厲害的東西
Your brain is wild, Mbwana.
你的野心很大, 波瓦那
We need to build the Buckingham Palace.
我們要蓋白金漢宮
Buckingham Palace?
白金漢宮?
Why not, eh?
為何不?
Get the Queen to move in
讓女皇搬過來
and then we can build the Eiffel Tower.
然後我們再蓋巴黎鐵塔
I prefer the Raj Mahal.
我比較想要Raj Mahal (飯店名)
You are too wild Mbwana.
你野心太大 波瓦那
I will kick you, I will kick you!
我要踢你, 我要踢你喔!
So you are taking pictures?
你在拍照嗎?
You look like one of those lesbians.
你就像那些蕾絲邊一樣
Just give me the pictures.
給我照片
Delete it, delete the picture.
刪掉它, 把照片刪掉
Okay, take it properly then.
好啦, 好好拍照
Look at this.
看這邊
That was a good one.
這張拍得很好
You look like an Italian lesbian
你看起來像個義大利蕾絲邊
Let me see that one.
讓我看一下
A Spanish lesbian,
長的像德羅巴(象牙海岸國家足球隊隊員)
with a Drogba face.
的西班牙蕾絲邊
You are jealous. Take another one.
你在忌妒我 再照一張
Do you think I have a best side
你覺得我有最好看的一面嗎?
or are they both equally better?
還是兩面都一樣好看?
I think they are both equally ugly, so it's okay!
我想他們一樣醜, 所以沒差!
Vogue, Vogue.
雜誌風, 雜誌風
You look like a buffoon.
你看起來像的蠢蛋
A baboon? I know many fine baboons.
狒狒 (英文發音與蠢蛋相近)? 我知道很多漂亮的狒狒
Did you see that? Did you see that?
你有看到嗎? 你有看到嗎?
Juma, Juma did you take the photo?
朱瑪, 朱瑪 你有照到嗎?
I did. I got the picture, look at it.
我有, 我有照到, 你看
Where are you going?
你要去哪?
To make some tourist dollar!
去賺觀光財囉!
Yes, this is quite something.
沒錯, 這真的很了不起
Zanzibar is fast becoming the world's capital
桑吉巴快速的成為
in the realm of giant fish.
巨魚歷史上的世界之都
Thousands of tourists are making the trip
成千上萬的觀光客
and heading to the most spectacular.
蜂擁而至
Hi everybody, raise your glasses to me, the Fish Man!
大家, 為我這位巨魚達人舉起你的酒杯吧!
More, more, more!
再來, 再來, 再來!
Go, go, I don't need you anyway,
走, 走, 反正我不需要你
I'll find my way, I'll find my way home
我知道路, 我自己可以回家
No room for you on the bus, old man.
公車上沒你的位置囉, 老人
Quite something.
了不起
Get back!
回來!